{
    "subject": "resource/Crytek_UK",
    "predicate": "property/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/Nottingham",
    "human_readable": "The location city of Crytek UK is Nottingham.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9133559465408325,
            "question": "Where is Crytek UK located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8848429918289185,
            "question": "Name the city that houses Crytek UK."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8660753965377808,
            "question": "In which city can you find Crytek UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8182743787765503,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of Crytek UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8028739094734192,
            "question": "In which city does Crytek UK operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7918686270713806,
            "question": "What is the location of Crytek UK's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7821574807167053,
            "question": "Crytek UK is based in what British city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7794708609580994,
            "question": "Where are the offices of Crytek UK situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7539477944374084,
            "question": "What city in the United Kingdom is home to Crytek UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5407336354255676,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit Crytek UK's offices, what city would you go to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location city of Crytek UK is Nottingham.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3212_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city in the United Kingdom is home to Crytek UK?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3212_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are the offices of Crytek UK situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3212_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Crytek UK is based in what British city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3212_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3212_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the location city of Crytek UK is indeed Nottingham. According to multiple documents, Crytek UK (formerly known as Free Radical Design) is based in Sandiacre, England, but it was later confirmed that they moved their offices to brand new ones in the central Nottingham Southreef development in 2010."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Crytek UK is based in Nottingham, England. This information supports the statement that the location city of Crytek UK is Nottingham."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}